Waste not what not, ends up being a good directive and it can lead to some exciting art.
This is a print, a print is a piece of art that has been replicated.
In other words, I had, it says two of six down here, I made six prints of this, you pull a print.
This is a litho-print.
I found that it got a little too black and once it gets too black, there's not a lot you can do with it.
Ink is permanent, you can't take it off, you can't erase it, it's there.
So, I had these six pieces of paper, it's very nice quality paper.
I like the quality of the blacks and I really like some of the texture, of the washes that happened, but the design itself isn't doing a whole lot.
What are you going to do with your art?
You can take pieces that don't work for you and see if you can bring them together, in another way, to make a piece of art.
What I did with this one was, I tore it, rather than cutting it, because the edges of the piece of paper were, themselves, not cut but had a decal edge, is what they call the rougher edges of paper.
I just tore them in irregular strips and when I laid them out, I found a really cool rhythm starting to build up.